https://cumberlandcaverns.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content 1437 Cumberland Caverns Road McMinnville, Tennessee 37110 P: 931-668-4396 | F: 931-668-5382 info@cumberlandcaverns.comOPEN YEAR ROUND 9am–5pm (CST) Daily Walking Tours leave out every hour on the hour. Rocky Topper Saturday (ages 6 and up) Sat. At 10 AM
Higgenbotham’s Revenge Saturday (ages 11 and up) Sat. At 2 PM Closed: Christmas Eve, Christmas Day, Thanksgiving DayDIRECTIONSRequest Donations ClosePrivacy PolicyWe use your personal information for providing and improving the service.By using the service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.*Cumberland Caverns (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://cumberlandcaverns.com/ (website / service).Information Collection And Use:While using our service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, other information (“Personal Information”).We collect this information for the purpose of providing the service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests / inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services.Log Data:We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.Cookies:Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our service, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.Behavioral Re-marketing:Cumberland Caverns uses re-marketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our service.Google:Google AdWords re-marketing service is provided by Google Inc.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page.Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page.AdRollAdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page.For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page.Do Not Track Disclosure:We support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the preferences or settings page of your web browser.Service Providers:We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our service, to provide the service on our behalf, to perform service-related services and / or to assist us in analyzing how our service is used.These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf, and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.Communications:We may use your personal information to contact you with newsletters, marketing, promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.Compliance With Laws:We will disclose your personal information where required to do so by law, subpoena, or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our service.Security:The security of your personal information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the personal information we have collected from you.International Transfer:Your information, including personal information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including personal information, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Links To Other Sites:Our service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s Privacy:Only persons age 18, or older have permission to access our service. Our service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (*children).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your children have provided us with personal information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy Policy:This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 28, 2015 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time, and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications, and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact Us:If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. Search for:
TicketsSpecialsRocky Topper SaturdayHiggenbotham’s Revenge SaturdayLantern TourApple Brandy Trail Guided HikeCavers Christmas PartyDaytime ToursDaily Walking TourSeason PassesFamily Fun TicketThings to Know – Daily Walking TourVIP Walking ToursDaytime AdventuresRocky Topper Adventure ReserveHiggenbotham’s Revenge Adventure ReserveParts Unknown AdventureLegacy Tour AdventureThings to Know When Planning a Caving TripOvernight AdventuresWhat Waits Below OvernightAll Around the Mountain OvernightAll-Inclusive Cardwell Mountain OvernightHiggenbotham’s OvernightParts Unknown OvernightLegacy Tour OvernightThings To Know When Planning An Overnight AdventureBring My GroupGroup Caving ToursCreation Light ShowChristian ToursEducational Field TripsCave News BlogConcertsMAR 27 – Edwin McCainMAR 28 – Chicks With HitsMAY 8 – The OutlawsMAY 29 – The Allman Betts BandCC Live MusicAbout UsDirectionsContact InformationHistoric National LandmarkShopping Cart
Login
Login Username or email address *
Password *
Remember me
Log in Lost your password?Register Email address *
Password * Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
Register
